<resources>

    <!-- The name that displays in Task Manager -->
    <string name="app_name">Cortez</string>

    <!-- Map Activity title -->
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Cortez</string>

    <!-- Info Activity title -->
    <string name="title_activity_info">InfoActivity</string>

    <!-- Cortez Audio Player title -->
    <string name="title_activity_imageviewer">ImageViewer</string>

    <!-- Cortez Audio Player title -->
    <string name="title_activity_audioplayer">AudioPlayer</string>

    <!-- Cortez Video Viewer title -->
    <string name="title_activity_videoviewer">VideoViewer</string>

    <!-- Cortez YouTube Viewer title -->
    <string name="title_activity_youtubeviewer">YouTubeViewer</string>

    <!-- Help Activity title -->
    <string name="title_activity_help">HelpActivity</string>

    <!-- Map Select title -->
    <string name="title_activity_map_select">Select Map</string>

    <!-- Launcher title -->
    <string name="title_activity_launcher">Cortez</string>

    <!-- Launcher 'Helpful Hint' text -->
    <string name="launcher_text">Cortez is a design suite for interactive adventures. It\’s a web/mobile app that allows you to create/view location-based info for exploring!</string>

    <!-- Geofence transition notification messages -->
    <string name="notifyGeofenceEnter">Geofence Entered</string>
    <string name="notifyGeofenceDwell">Geofence Dwell</string>
    <string name="notifyGeofenceExit">Geofence Exited</string>

    <!-- Action menu items -->
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_help">Help</string>

    <!-- Help Screen Strings -->
    <string name="HelpActivityContentForMapActivity">&lt;h1&gt;Map Screen&lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        The Map screen is where the Markers from your selected map will be displayed.&lt;br /&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        You should see a number of Markers defined by the map\'s creators. When you click on them, you will be brought to the Info screen for that Marker, where you will see information about that location.&lt;br /&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        If you are too far away from a Marker, though, you may not be able to see pictures or videos. Try getting closer!&lt;br /&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        If you don\'t see any Markers nearby, try zooming out; The map\'s content may be centered elsewhere.&lt;br /&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        To zoom to your current location, press the Target icon in the upper-right corner of the screen.&lt;br /&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        Press your phone\'s &lt;b&gt;Back&lt;/b&gt; button to return to the Map screen.
    </string>
    <string name="HelpActivityContentForInfoActivity">&lt;h1&gt;Info Screen&lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        The Info screen displays information about the Marker that you selected.&lt;br /&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        If you are too far away from the Marker, you may not be able to see anything but the text information. Try getting closer to see videos or pictures!&lt;br /&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        Not every Marker will have video or pictures. Only those enabled by the map\'s creators. If you want more, ask them!&lt;br /&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        Press your phone\'s &lt;b&gt;Back&lt;/b&gt; button to return to the Info screen.
    </string>
    <string name="HelpActivityContentForYoutubeActivity">&lt;h1&gt;Youtube Screen&lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        This is the Help Screen content for the Youtube Activity screen.&lt;br /&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        This is where you will view Youtube playlists associated with a location. It should behave just like any other Youtube player!&lt;br /&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        Press your phone\'s &lt;b&gt;Back&lt;/b&gt; button to return to the Youtube screen.
    </string>
    <string name="HelpActivityContentForMapSelectActivity">&lt;h1&gt;Map Select Screen&lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        This is the Help Screen content for the Map Select screen. &lt;br /&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        Here, you will find a list of the maps you have downloaded. Click on one to open its associated map and begin exploring! &lt;br /&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        If you have not downloaded any maps (or you want to download more), tap the top-right of your screen and select "Add A Map" to open up the list of maps available from our website. The map will be downloaded to your device (carrier data charges may apply) and automatically opened! &lt;br /&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        Press your phone\'s &lt;b&gt;Back&lt;/b&gt; button to return to the Map Select screen.
    </string>
</resources>
